BERNIMAN GOFINDO MALAU

(+62) 812-8718-9069 | govindo1706@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/bgofindo-malau Sukabumi, West Java, Indonesia, 43123

About me

Introducing my name is Berniman Gofindo Malau. I am a student at Nusa Putra University majoring in Informatics Engineering class of 2019. My expertise includes: IT Support Hardware and Software, Software Programming and Web Developer programming languages (Front-end and Backend) such as Python, XML, MySQL database, PostgreSQL, Javascript, HTML&CSS, PHP Native, Odoo Framework, Laravel Framework, and Bootstrap Framework, highly committed, like work challenges, and willing to take risks to achieve my goals.

Education

Nusa Putra University - Sukabumi, Indonesia

2019 - Present

Informatics Engineering

- Informatics Engineering Student Association
- English Club
- Basketball member

Siantar Narumonda Public High School 1 - Toba Samosir, North Sumatra

2015 - 2018

Sains

- 2017 football team captain
- 3rd place in Toba Samosir district high school football tournament

Skills, Achievements, and Characteristics

- Softskills: Problem Solving, Teamwork, Kreatif, Critical Thingking.
- Hardskills: IT Support Hardware and Software, Programming like Python, XML, Mysql database, PostgreSQL, Javascript, HTML&CSS, Wordpress Building, PHP Native, Odoo Framework, Laravel Framework and Bootstrap Framework.
- Projects (2022): Quality Control Product Development ERP PT Hashmicro
- **Projects** (2022): Inventory Product Development ERP PT Hashmicro
- Projects (2022): Inventory Project ERP Maju Bersama- PT Hashmicro
- Projects (2022): Inventory Project ERP Vinco- PT Hashmicro
- **Projects** (2022): Build a website for the Buniwangi village government with Laravel Framework
- **Journal Publish** (2022): Implementation of Internet Network Mikrotik Load Balancing at Pardamean Sibisa, Ajibata, Toba Samosir, North Sumatra
- Certification (2022): Mikrotik Certified Network Assosiate (MTCNA)

Work Experience

PT. Hashmicro x Kampus Merdeka – Software Programmer Intern

Feb 2022 - Des 2022

- Software development for Hashmicro's FrontEnd and Backend Websites with Odoo
- Development of Inventory Project with Python Programming, XML and Javascript and PostgreSQL Database
- Software development cycle (SDLC) and several types of project methodologies structure such as Water Fall, Agile, and Scrum
- Paradigm programming
- Set in Product and Project Development

Buniwangi Village Government Surade - Web Developer

Feb 2022 - Mar 2022

Build a Buniwangi Village Government Website with HTML & CSS, PHP Native and MYSQL Database

Badan Pelaksana Otorita Danau Toba - IT Support

- Jul 2021 Sept 2021
- check and ensure all computers that are used by users can be used
- Perform data backup
- Install and configure antivirus for computer security
- Repair computer network problems
- system support software such as printers and scanners can operate

Administation - CV Karang Taruna Pardamean Sibisa

Jan 2021 - Jun 2021

- Preparation/submission of letters of interest for business entities
- Compile business entity data archives
- Taking care of business entity`s needs/equipment

Organization Experience

Informatics Engineering Student Association

2019 - Present

Information of communication

- Delivering all forms of information and in charge of all kinds of information in the field of design and photo & video editing
- Provide information that is actual and factual and useful for students
- Presenting interesting and creative content through sharing social media and other information and communication media
- Filter real information to avoid information that doesn't really happen